Pride Center of the Capital Region; Records apap361
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Events, 1973-2017; 3.5 cubic ft.
  This series contains records related to the events of the Pride Center and other LGBTQ organizations. The Pride Center is in charge of planning Capital Pride. Records in this series include documentation relating to the planning of Captial Pride, as well as photos from the actual celebration. This series also includes records related to the center's awards dinners, themed nights, and events at the center itself. This series also contains records related to the events that membrs of the center could attend. These records include talks from the SUNY Gay Alliance. Stonewall Rememberance Days, and other organization in th Capital Region and New York City. This series also contains CD's from the Pride Events. Some folders are restricted due to personal information. Please consult an archivist before use.
  - 2nd Annual Youth Barbeque - RESTRICTED, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 2nd Anniversary Dinner Hudson Mohawk Business and professional Association, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 4th Annual 3 Factory Street Chicken House Beer Party and Social Bash, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 5th Anniversary of Loving Couples, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 10th Anniversary Celebration Reception for Refer Switchboard, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 20th Birthday Party, 1992 December 17 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1997-Capital Pride (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1998-Capital Pride (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1998-Capital Pride (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Capital Pride (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Capital Pride (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 2000 Capital Pride (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 2001 Capital Pride (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 2001 Capital Pride (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 2002 Capital Pride (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 2002 Capital Pride (Cd 1)
  - 2002 Capital Pride Logistics (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 2003 Capital Pride (1 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 2003 Capital Pride (2 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 2003 Capital Pride (3 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 2003 Capital Pride (Cd 2)
  - 2003 Capital Pride Backup (Cd 3)
  - 2003 Capital Pride Volunteers - RESTRICTED (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 2003 Capital Pride Program (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 2004 Capital Pride (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 2004 Capital Pride (Cd 4)
  - 2005 Capital Pride (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 2005 Capital Pride (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 2005 Capital Pride (Cd 5)
  - 2005 Capital Pride Contact List - RESTRICTED (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 2005 Capital Pride Guide (Cd 6)
  - 2006 Pride (Cd 7)
  - 2006 Capital Pride (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 2006 Capital Pride (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 2006 Capital Pride (Cd 8)
  - 2006 Capital Pride-Steering Committee - RESTRICTED (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 2007 Capital Pride (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 2007 Capital Pride (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 2008 Capital Pride (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 2009 Capital Pride (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 2009 Capital Pride (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Capital Pride, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 2011 Capital Pride (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 2011 Capital Pride (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 2013 Capital Pride (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 2013 Capital Pride (Cd 9)
  - 2013 Capital Pride (Flat-file 1)
  - 2015 Capital Pride (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - A Gay Day in New York, 1981 September 26 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - A Get Together, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - A Vocal Recital, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - A Very Natural Thing, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Aging and Disabled Friendly Community Empowerment Kick Off, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Albany County Mental Health Association-Summer Breakthrough, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Ann Arbor Film Fest, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Annual Fall Gay Dance, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Annual Picnic, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - As a Three Dollar Bill, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Awards Dinner, 1979; 1981; 1983; 1985-1987; 1992 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    General
    1998/1999
  - Annual Awards Dinner Attendee List (1 of 4)- RESTRICTED, 2005-2009 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Annual Awards Dinner Attendee List (2 of 4)- RESTRICTED, 2005-2009 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Annual Awards Dinner Attendee List (3 of 4)- RESTRICTED, 2005-2009 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Annual Awards Dinner Attendee List (4 of 4)- RESTRICTED, 2005-2009 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Award Dinner-Photos (1 of 2), 2001-2002; Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Award Dinner-Photos (1 of 2), 2001-2002; Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Backup, 2005 November 4 (Cd 10)
  - Benefit for the Capital Defense Fund, Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Book Club, Undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Boston Gay Men's Chorus, 2000; Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Bowling Events, Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Bus Trip to New York City, Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Cabaret: A Night in Greenwich Village, Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Cabaret Theater, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Capital Pride Resolutions, 1999; 2004-2006; 2008-2009; 2011; 2014 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Capital Region Adoption and Foster Care Consortium, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Cavafy-Days of 1903, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - CDGLCC Superheroes Volunteer-Appreciation Party, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Celebration Stonewall, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Changing Norms of Sexuality-Father Paul Shanley, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Charlie Murphy Events, 1982; Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Chefs of Our Community, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Christian Church (Disciplines of Christ)-Worship Service, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Christopher Columbus Discovers Gay America Weekend, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Christopher Street Parade, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Clean Up/ Fix Day, Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Cocktail Parties, 1976; 1979; 1981; 1985; Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Coffee House Performance, Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Cupid's Valentine Gayla (Loving Couples) Program, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Dances, Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Dear Liar, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Demonstration Against the Singer Company, Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Defy the Supreme Court, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Dance and Picnic-Contra/Square Dance, Undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Dignity/Albany First Annual Spring Picnic, Undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Dinners at the Center, Undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Disco Dance, Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Diversity Planning Presentation, 2005 (Cd 11)
  - Drag Show, Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Dried Blood Spots-Training Agenda, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Empire State Pride Agenda Honors Jim Perry, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Events at the Egg, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Events at Empire State Plaza, Undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Film Fest, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - First Day of the Rest of Our Lives, Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Frank Smith Art Shows, Undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Free University, Undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Gay and Lesbian Pride Calendar Week, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Gay and Lesbian Pride Days, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Gay Cabaret: Friday the 13th Massacre, Undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Gay Cuban Refugee Benefit Concert, Undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Gay Episcopalians and Their Friends In the Capital District, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Gay Freedom Days, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Gay March on Washington D.C., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Gay Pride Awareness at SUNYA, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Gay Pride Week, Undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Gay Rites of Spring Dance, Undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Gay Youth: Straight From the Heart, Undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Gertrude Stein/Alive Picnic, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Gertrude Stein Book Collective, Undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Goodbye Summer Pina Coladas-Meet and Talk with Sixth Ward Alderwoman Hon. Nancy Burton, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Great Escape Trip, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Happy Birthday CDGCC, Undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - History Brunch-Harvey Milk Speech, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Holiday Party, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Homosexuality Information Day, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Homosexuality/Sexuality in Prisons, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Invisible Minority: A Straight Look at the Reality of Gay Life, Undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Jim Perry Memorial Service, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - John Boyd Thatcher State Park Picnic, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Joseph P. Borgovini-"20th West", Undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Joshua Dunning Powell Scholarship Fund for LGBTQ Youth-Scholarship Awardee Breakfast, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Kevin Thibodeau's Farewell Party, Undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Key Bank Run for Pride 5k Run and Rainbow Fun Run- RESTRICTED, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Last Rites of Summer Picnic, Undated (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Lesbian and Gay Pride Days-10 Years, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Lesbian Comic, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - List of Events, Undated (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Loving Couples Benefit, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - March on Albany for Lesbian and Gay Rights, 1980 April 12 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Marriage Rally, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Marriage Rally, 2006 (Cd 12)
  - Maxine Feldman Concert, Undated (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Meet and Greet-Michael Broderick New Executive Director, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Midstate Speedway, Undated (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Movie Nights, Undated (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - National March on Washington For Lesbian and Gay rights, 1979; 1987 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - New York State Coalition of Gay Organizations Brunch, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - New York State Now Lobbyist Barbra Brundage Talk, Undated (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - New Yorkers Rally for Human Rights, Undated (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - NGTF Weekend, Undated (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - No More Miami's! Build The Gay Rights Movement, Undated (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - P.A.G.E.-Camp-Out, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Party at John Nehrich's, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Party is the People- A Tea Dance, Undated (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Photos-Oversized, 1972-1997; Undated (Flat-file 2)
  - Picnic Afternoon at Glen Bridge Road Park, Undated (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Picnic Committee Volunteers, Undated (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Pictures Burned, 2005 November 3 (Cd 13)
  - Pride Calendar, 1978; Undated (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Pride Center Gala, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Pride Days, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Pride Parade Photos (1 of 4), 1972-1973; 1997; 2001; 2003; Undated (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Pride Parade Photos (2 of 4), 1972-1973; 1997; 2001; 2003; Undated (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Pride Parade Photos (3 of 4), 1972-1973; 1997; 2001; 2003; Undated (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Pride Parade Photos (4 of 4), 1972-1973; 1997; 2001; 2003; Undated (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Pride Posters, 1998 (Flat-file 3)
  - Proclamation, 1997-1999; 2005-2008; 2010; 2014; Undated (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Proclamations and Resolutions, 2000; 2009; 2015 (Flat-file 4)
  - Progressions Concert Series, 2005 November 4 (Cd 14)
  - Protest the Raid on the Club Capital Bath and Alleged Police Harassment of the Gays, Undated (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Quit Smoking Program, Undated (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Rainbow Rumble Softball Tournament CDGLCC Vs. Two Rivers LGBT Outdoor Club, 2008 August 9 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Reception Honoring Martina Navratilova, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Region II Dignity Conference, Undated (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Regional Day of Recollection, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Religious Leadership In the Struggle for Human Rights, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Remember Pearl Harbor, Undated (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Renewing the Center: A Responsible Strategy for Stability and Growth, Undated (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Richard Roy- Dinner, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Saratoga Festival: A benefit for the Citizens' Committee on Mental Health, Undated (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Sensual Sounds of Jason Blume, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Shella Healy and Hon Debra, Undated (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Silent Auction, Undated (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Sloansville House, Undated (Vhs-c 1)
  - Speaker Series, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Special Events Flyer, Undated (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Stars, M.C. Bar Nights, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Stone Wall Dance- Under the Stars, Undated (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Steamers- New York Shakespeare Festival at Lincoln Center, Undated (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Sunday Evening Tea Dances, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Sunya Gay Alliance- Dance Disco, Undated (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Sunya Gay Alliance- Hank Baron, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Suzanne Westenhoerer, Undated (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Ten Percent Revenue, Undated (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Theatre Party- Suddenly Last Summer by Tennessee Williams, Undated (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Tom Wilson in Concert, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Towards A Unified Lesbian and Gay Movement in New York State in the 1980s (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Unidentified- Softball, 2008 (Cd 15)
  - United States Church of Christ in Goshen- Fourteenth Sunday After Pentecost, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Uptown/Downtown Discotheque Birthday Celebration, Undated (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Valentines Gayla, 2000 February 12 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Vocal Recital, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Wedding Invitations, 1967-1977 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Werner Paul Kuhn, Esq- Second Annual Open House, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - When Baby Makes Three or Four More, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Winter Solstice Open House, Undated (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Women of Excellence, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - You're Invited to meet Midge Costanza, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Yule Festival, Undated (Box 4, Folder 124)
- Subject Files, 1973-2015; 13.5 cubic ft.
  - A Dead Moms Protest, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A Different Light Bookstore, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A Gay Bibliography, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - A History of Lambda, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Albany Friends of the Center-Banadana, Undated (Oversize 9)
  - A Time to Speak: A Collection of Contemporary Statements From U.S. Catholic Sources on Homosexuality, Gay Ministry, and Social Justice, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - A Working Paper: Institutional Self-Evaluation of Sex Discrimination by Institutions of Higher Education, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - About Our Children, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Activism on Wheels, Undated (Flat-file 1)
  - Actual Case of Homosexuality and Homophobia- John Morse, 1991 April 12 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Adoption in New York, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Advertisers for Loving Couples, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Advancing LGBT Colorado: The Center, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - AIDs Council of North Eastern New York, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Albany- Colonie Regional Chamber of Commerce, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Albany Community Police Relations Board, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Albany Report- The Men's Project, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Albany/Schenectady- League of Arts, 1998-1999; Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - ALICE, 1980; 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annual Awards Dinner-Sign, 2009 (Oversize 9)
  - Are You Straight? Are You Gay? Are You Sure?, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Arcadie- Institution to All to Assist at Our Congress, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Arts Media Directory, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Beth Suter-Radio Spot Teen Suicide Panel, Undated (Floppy-disk 1)
  - Board Website Fast Fund Backups, Undated (Cd 1)
  - Box Cutters, Undated (Artifact-box 1)
  - Brochures, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Brooklyn Now, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bruner and Bruner Vs. City of Albany Common Council, Mayor Gerald Jennings, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Business Cards, Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Calander-1985 (Oversize 7, Folder 1)
  - Can you Rely on Condoms?, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Capital Area Coalition for Human Rights, 1977-1979; Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Capital District Gay & Lesbian Community Council, Inc., Undated (Vhs 1)
  - Capital District Gay Political Caucus, 1977; 1979-1981; Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Capital Newspapers Group, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Capital Pride Center STAFF-Photos, 2013 May 7 (Dvd 1)
  - Capital Region AID's Task Force, 2002; Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Capital Region Gay/Lesbian Organizations and Services, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Cards, 1985-1986; 1994; Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Cathedral of All Saints- Funeral of Paul K. Miller, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Cartoon Drawing- Kevin Druce, Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Casswood Cup, Undated (Floppy-disk 2)
  - Categorization Study, Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - CDGLCC's 40 years of Pride 1970-2010 Paper Weight (Artifact-box 2)
  - CDGLCC Tape 1- Capital, Ext cc, ESP, B-Roll, Photos, Pamelo Means, Undated (Mini-dv 1)
  - CDGLCC Tape 2- Interviews, Keith, Mike Mc. Pt 1, Undated (Mini-dv 2)
  - CDGLCC Tape 3- Interviews, Mike Mc. Pt 2 B-Roll, Gloria D, Sudam, Undated (Mini-dv 3)
  - CDGLCC Tape 4- Pamela Means, AIDS Walk, Undated (Mini-dv 4)
  - CDGLCC Tape 5-Nick: Mom, Rose, Dawn, B-Roll, Undated (Mini-dv 5)
  - CDGLCC Tape 6- B-Roll,Tabletops, Libby, B-Roll Center, Undated (Mini-dv 6)
  - CDGLCC Tape 7- B-Roll, Undated (Mini-dv 7)
  - CDGLCC Dub Master, 2004 (Mini-dv 8)
  - CDGLCC DVD Copy, 2004 (Dvd 3)
  - CDGLCC Finance Backup, 2005-2006 (Cd 2)
  - CDGLCC-Sevendays, Undated (Floppy-disk 3)
  - CDGLCC V.1, Undated (Dvd 2)
  - City of Albany Common Council- Alderman Keith C. St, John, Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Civil Rights Series- Denise LeClare, Undated (Dvd 4)
  - Coming out at Work, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Community Foundation for the Capital Region, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Community Pride Booklet, Undated (Zip-disk 1)
  - Community Song, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Computer System, Undated (Floppy-disk 4)
  - Correspondence- John Morse (1 of 2), 1989-1996 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence- John Morse (2 of 2), 1989-1996 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Creating Change- Speakers Bureau Intensive, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Defend "Mike" Defend Yourself, Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Directory of Services, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Domestic Partnerships come to Albany, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Education Chapter of a Legislative Guide to Gay Rights, Undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Democratic Club Award, 1993 (Oversize 7, Folder 2)
  - Equality, Undated (Oversize 7, Folder 3)
  - Equal Times: Act Up/ Koch and A Deadly Disease, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Flyer for Center, 1992; 2000 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Forbundet AF, 1948-1980 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Freedom Travel, Undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - From the Heart, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Gay Alliance of Genesee Valley, 1979; 1992 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Gay and Lesbian Cuban Refugees, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Gay and Women's Alliance for Responsible Media- Media Standards, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Gay Community Center of the District of Columbia, Undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Gay Men's Health Project, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Gay Rights National Lobby, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Gay Students Association, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Gays in the Boy Scouts, Undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Gay Under Nazi Rule, Undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Good Guys, Bad Guys, and the Gay Guys, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Good News Metropolitan Community Center, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Group of Sexology and Criminology, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Hamilton Hill Art Center, Undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Harm Reduction Coalition, Undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Hawaii Equal Rights Marriage Project, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Headshots, 1972; 1978; 1993; 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Health Disparities in Sexual Minorities Along the Life Cycle: A Beginning Community Discussion, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Historic Albany Foundation, Undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - HIV Antibody Test: Pretest Information for Research Subjects, Undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Homosexuals in China, Undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Homosexuals Intransigent, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - HP B105 Update, Undated (Floppy-disk 5)
  - Hudson Valley LGBTQ Community Center, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Human Rights Campaign, Undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - In These Times: A Series of Forums on Contemporary Affairs, Undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Inauguration of Bill Clinton and Al Gore, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Jen Valetutto, Undated (Cd 3)
  - Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Laptop Docs 1, Undated (Cd 4)
  - Laptop Docs 2, 2003 (Cd 5)
  - Laptop Doc, Undated (Cd 6)
  - Lark Street Champagne on the Park Honoree Award, Undated (Oversize 8)
  - Lea DeLaria- Poster, 2004 April 3 (Cd 7)
  - Left Card Safe Copy, 2005-2006 (Cd 8)
  - Legend of Hedgehog Boy- By Rene Capone, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Lesbian and Gay Liberation and Socialism, Undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Community Center, 1983; 2002-2003; Undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Letters to Congressmen for Funding, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Loan, IRS, and Pride Budget, 1995; 1997; 1998; 2000 (Floppy-disk 6)
  - love is in the Air, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Love Making a Family: Living in Lesbian and Gay Families, Undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Mail.cdglcc.org.iaf IAF File, Undated (Floppy-disk 7)
  - Marching Contingence, Undated (Floppy-disk 8)
  - Marching Into the 90's- NYS Lesbian and Gay Lobby March on Albany, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Marriage Equality, 2003-2004; Undated (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Maruel Entertainment Company Correspondence, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Men Out, Undated (Floppy-disk 9)
  - Metropolitian Community Church of the Capital District, 1980; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Misc 2004 Backup Files (Cd 9)
  - Music, 1975-1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Names Project, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - National Conference on Gay and Lesbian Issues, 1979 October 26; 1978 October 28 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - National Gay Task Force (1 of 2), 1976-1980; Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - National Gay Task Force (2 of 2), 1976-1980; Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - National Organization for Watch- new York State Annual Convention and New Activist Training Institute, 2006 October 21-2006 October 22 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - National Youth Advocacy Coalition, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Negatives, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Network Advocacy Day, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - New York Americans for Democratic Action, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - New York City Center Happenings, Undated (Oversize 7, Folder 4)
  - New York State Coalition of Gay Organizations, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - New York State Equal Rights Amendment: It's Legal Effect, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - New York State Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Health and Human Services Network Annual Meeting and Retreat, 2009 September 14-2009 September 15 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - News clips (1 of 2), 1974-1982; 1993-1994; 1997; Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - News clips (1 of 2), 1974-1982; 1993-1994; 1997; Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Non-Profits in the Dark About Liability Risks, Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - North American Man/ Boy Love Association, 1980; 1982 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - North American Speakers Bureau Directory, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - OCR Interpretation of the Title IX Regulations as it Concerns Sex Separate Departments of Physical Education and Athletics, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Onedc.Doc For Pride Guide, Undated (Floppy-disk 10)
  - Our Bodies, Our Selves: A Book By and For Women, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - People Vs. Rice, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Peoples College of Law of the National Lawyers Guild, Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Planned Parenthood- Healthcare Education, Advocacy, Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Plaque, Undated (Oversize 9)
  - Play Script, Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Photos of the Center, 1970; 1989-1990; 1995-1996; Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)